Miss Yujia Chen

Mobile Phone: +61-0452524514

Email: yujia.chenn@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

Profile

I am a highly motivated computer-science postgraduate with a solid background in programming. I am skilled in Java, Python, JavaScript and Flutter with a strong interest in developing interesting apps in GitHub. I am experienced in working at startup companies with a focus on delivering outcomes weekly.

Education Background

Australian National University, 2021-2023

Canberra, Australia

Major: Master of Computing

GPA: 6.69/7.0

Honor: Chancellor's Letter of Commendation in 2021 and 2023.

Dongguk University, 2019 Seoul, Korea

Major: Mathematics

GPA: 4.5/4.5

Ningbo University, 2016-2020 Ningbo, China

Major: Bachelor of Mathematical Teaching Education

GPA: 86.21/100

Skills

• Soft Skills: Team Collaboration | Effective Communication | Self-Motivated Learning

- Technical Skills: Java | Python | JavaScript | React.js | Node.js | PostgreSQL | Django |
 MongoDB | Firebase | Express | TailwindCSS | Vite | AndroidStudio | Flutter | Dart
- **Development Practices:** Git version control | Agile Project Management

Professional Experience

Web Developer of AccentedAl Part-time

Canberra, Australia Dec 2023 ~ Mar 2024

- ➤ Developed and maintained a language learning web application using TypeScript and React.js, including a Google Chrome extension.
- > Implemented a responsive login page using TailwindCSS, ensuring compatibility across various devices.
- ➤ Established WebSocket communication between the frontend and a speech recognition server for real-time audio streaming.
- Persisted recording metadata in database using GraphQL and Hasura.
- > Coordinated with team members using Linear for goal setting and tracking,

contributing to successful project milestones.

• Academic Tutor in Australian National University

Feb 2023 ~ Now

Provided academic support in courses including Software Construction, Network Information Systems, Web Development, and Relational Databases.

➤ Coordinated with other tutors and course instructors to organize lab activities, promoting engaging, efficient and welcoming lab sessions.

Received excellent feedback from students through SELT evaluations.

React Developer of MochiLabs Internship

Canberra, Australia July 2022 ~ June 2023

➤ Developed features for a note-taking application using JavaScript, React.js, ProseMirror, TailwindCSS and Playwright testing.

Implemented essential features such as LateX extension integration, Toggle-list insertion, authentication and verification.

➤ Collaborated closely with a team of developers, conducting version control using Gitlab.

Worked closely with a development team in an Agile environment, managing version control through GitLab and participating in regular client meetings, communicating with clients and refining issues efficiently.

Referees

> Alasdair Tran

Position: Founder of AccentedAI

Email: alasdair.tran@anu.edu.au

> Bernardo Pereira Nunes

Position: Convenor of Software Construction

Email: Bernardo.Nunes@anu.edu.au

> Sabrina Caldwell

Position: Convenor of Web Development and Design

Email: sabrina.caldwell@anu.edu.au